module.exports = [
 {
   question: 'I\'m mad as hell and I\'m not gonna take this anymore!',
   a: 'Faux News',
   b: 'Apocalypse Now',
   c: 'Network',
   d: 'Serpico',
   answer: 'c'
 },
 {
   question: '... Iâ€™m funny how, I mean funny like I\'m a clown, I amuse you?',
   a: 'Goodfellas',
   b: 'Ace Ventura',
   c: 'My Cousin Viiney',
   d: 'Eight Heads in a Duffle Bag',
   answer: 'a'
 },
 {
   question: 'Aziz, light!',
   a: 'Total Recall',
   b: 'The Fifth Element',
   c: 'Independence Day',
   d: 'Equilibrium',
   answer: 'b'
 },
 {
   question: 'Mathematics is the only true universal language.',
   a: 'Arrival',  
   b: 'Contact',
   c: 'A.I.',
   d: 'Event Horizon',
   answer: 'b'
 },
 {
   question: 'The more you drive, the less intelligent you are.',
   a: 'Repo Men',
   b: 'Paris Texas',
   c: 'Slacker',
   d: 'Repo Man',
   answer: 'd'
 },
 {
   question: 'My biological clock is [stomps on the porch] TICKING LIKE THIS...',
   a: 'My Cousin Vinny',
   b: 'The Nice Guys',
   c: 'Boyhood',
   d: 'Before Midnight',
   answer: 'a'
 },
 {
   question: 'I never saved anything for the swim back.',
   a: 'Dark City',
   b: 'Moon',
   c: 'Gattaca',
   d: 'The Abyss',
   answer: 'c'
 },
 {
   question: 'Water?  Like out of the toilet?',
   a: 'Beavis and Butt-head Do America',
   b: 'Team America',
   c: 'Office Space',
   d: 'Idiocracy',
   answer: 'd'
 },
 {
   question: 'Naga..Naga..Not gonna work here anymore...',
   a: 'Office Space',
   b: 'Clerks',
   c: 'Tommy Boy',
   d: 'Anchorman',
   answer: 'a'
 },
 {
   question: 'Game over man, game over!',
   a: 'Alien',
   b: 'Aliens',
   c: 'Alien 3',
   d: 'Alien: Resurrection',
   answer: 'b'
 },
];

